[
  {
    "id":"1",
    "question": "1.Which of the following is not a Java feature?",
    "options": [
      "A)Object-oriented",
      "B)Portable",
      "C)Dynamic",
      "D)Use of pointers"
    ],
    "CorrectAnswer": "D)Use of pointers",
    "YourAnswer":null
  },
  {
    "id":"2",
    "question": "2.Which of these is used to find and fix bugs in Java programs?",
    "options": ["A)JVM", "B)JRE", "C)JDK", "D)JDB"],
    "CorrectAnswer": "D)JDB",
    "YourAnswer":null
  },
  {
    "id":"3",
    "question": "3.What is the return type of the hashCode() method in Java?",
    "options": ["A)Object", "B)int", "C)long", "D)void"],
    "CorrectAnswer": "B)int",
    "YourAnswer":null
  },
  {
    "id":"4",
    "question": "4.Which keyword is used to inherit a class in java?",
    "options": ["A)this", "B)super", "C)extends", "D)implements"],
    "CorrectAnswer": "C)extends",
    "YourAnswer":null
  },
  {
    "id":"5",
    "question": "5.Which of the following is a marker interface?",
    "options": ["A)Runnable", "B)Serializable", "C)Comparable", "D)Cloneable"],
    "CorrectAnswer": "B)Serializable",
    "YourAnswer":null
  },
  {
    "id":"6",
    "question": "6.Which method is called automatically called when object is created?",
    "options": ["A)main()", "B)start", "C)constructor", "D)init()"],
    "CorrectAnswer": "C)constructor",
    "YourAnswer":null
  },
  {
    "id":"7",
    "question": "7.Which of the following is true about the final keyword in Java?",
    "options": [
      "A)It can be used with classes but not methods",
      "B)It prevents inheritance and modification",
      "C)It makes a variable mutable",
      "D)It is used only in interfaces"
    ],
    "CorrectAnswer": "B)It prevents inheritance and modification",
    "YourAnswer":null
  },
  {
    "id":"8",
    "question": "8.What is the size of int data type in Java?",
    "options": ["A)8 bits", "B)16 bits", "C)32 bits", "D)64 bits"],
    "CorrectAnswer": "C)32 bits",
    "YourAnswer":null
  },
  {
    "id":"9",
    "question": "9.Which of the following can be used to handle exceptions in Java?",
    "options": ["A)try-catch", "B)throw", "C)throws", "D)All of th above"],
    "CorrectAnswer": "D)All of the above",
    "YourAnswer":null
  },
  {
    "id":"10",
    "question": "10.Which collections class allows you to store unique elements and has no defined order?",
    "options": ["A)List", "B)Set", "C)Map", "D)Queue"],
    "CorrectAnswer": "B)Set",
    "YourAnswer":null
  }
]
